Preliminary Guide to the Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project Records, 1994-2000
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project records 1994-2000
Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project
0.6 linear feet Extent: 450 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.01308
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The collection was a gift from the Project in June 2000.
Historical Note
The Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project was founded in 1994 with the mission to promote awareness of women's history in the Raleigh/Durham/Chapel Hill area of North Carolina.
Collection Overview
The collection documents the activities of the Project, administrative and otherwise. Included are mailing lists (including an electronic file), newsletters, photographs, stationery, program and publicity ideas, old program lists, clippings, materials about other women's history groups, the Triangle Community Foundation proposal, non-profit status information, training materials, awards, past school projects, school visit evaluations, reports and surveys, newsletters, grant information, outreach materials, flyers and press releases, project ideas, and study group materials
Subject Headings
Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project; Women -- Social conditions; Women -- Societies and clubs; Oral history; Women-North Carolina-History
Contents of Collection
- Accession #2000-0269
  Materials in this accession span the dates 1994 through 2000.
  - Newsletters (Box 1)
  - Grants (Box 1)
  - Current Outreach Materials (Box 1)
  - Old Flyers and Press Releases (Box 1)
  - TMWP Study Group (Box 1)
  - Project Ideas (Box 1)
  - Contribution Analysis 1998 (Box 1)
  - 5-Year Report (Box 1)
  - 1998 Survey Results (Box 1)
  - School Visit Evaluations (Box 1)
  - TWS Training, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - School Project Past (Box 1)
  - Non Profit Status (Box 1)
  - Awards (Box 1)
  - TWS Training, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Telling Stories Volunteers TEAM / Recruit (Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1)
  - Other WH Groups Chicago (Box 2)
  - Triangle Community Foundation Proposal (Box 2)
  - Old Mailing Lists (Box 2)
  - Triangle Multicultural Women's History Project Past Documents (Box 2)
  - Program Ideas (Box 2)
  - Old Program Lists (Box 2)
  - Publicity Ideas (Box 2)
  - Stationery (Box 2)